<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Kale Stahl&#39;s Personal Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Kale Stahl&#39;s Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/</guid>
      <description>I am currently supported with funding as an NSF Graduate Research Fellow.&#xA;In general, I am interested in PDE and their applications to physics. I don&amp;rsquo;t have an official advisor at the moment, but I have been working on some introductory problems with Dr. Isaac Harric the past few semesters. At the moment I have been working on projects with numerical solutions to the Biharmonic scattering problem with approximate far-field data using a MUSIC algorithm and the Born approximation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cv/</guid>
      <description>Click here to see my current CV.&#xA;Publications in Referreed Journals D.L. Nguyen, K. Stahl, and T. Truong. A new sampling indicator function for stable imaging of periodic scattering media in Inverse Problems, Volume 39, Number 6, May 9, 2023. Link: https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1361-6420/acce5f/meta arXiv: https://arxiv.org/abs/2205.01206 Expository Works Undergraduate Honors Thesis: &amp;ldquo;On the Factorization Method for Inverse Scattering Problems&amp;rdquo; [pdf]&#xA;Lecture Notes Lecture Notes on Sobolev Inequalities [pdf] Lecture Notes on Bipolar Green&amp;rsquo;s Functions [pdf] Lecture Notes on Discrete Mathematics [pdf] Notes on Lie Algebras for Mathematical Physics [pdf] Some Notes on Scattering Resonances [pdf] Purdue Qualifying Exam Study Materials MA 530 Complex Analysis [pdf] MA 553 Abstract Algebra [pdf] MA 544 Real Analysis [pdf] MA 554 Linear Algebra [pdf] Presentations Upcoming None upcoming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>I am originally from Topeka, KS and I completed my undergrad in Mathematics and Physics at Kansas State University. I came to Purdue because their Math department is one of the few in the country that actually has a research group for Scattering Theory. After my PhD, my goal is to stay in academia and teach and conduct research full time. Given the current climate and job market I am flexible in that goal however&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Overview of the Sun \&amp; Moon through Lost Thunder Format</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/sum-lot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/sum-lot/</guid>
      <description>The Sun and Moon era of the Pokemon TCG is looked back on extremely fondly by competitively players, and rightly so. After the dominance of big-basic strategies in the Black and White era, and them continuing into XY due to the lackluster Mega Evolution mechanic, it was exciting to see the evolving Pokemon GX take over the reigns. With the introduction of the first few Sun and Moon sets, many of the less than desirable attributes of the XY era persisted: an over reliance on &amp;ldquo;turbo&amp;rdquo; item cards, basic pokemon dominating the format, and supporters that were extremely powerful with no negative impact on deck consistency.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
